Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/seyi-oyeniyi-a89b39233 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Microsoft Azure
MySQL
ASP.NET Core

Seyi Oyeniyi

.Net Developer | C# | Software Engineer Lagos State, Nigeria

Summary

I am a full stack software developer with over 4 years' experience. I have experience developing startup application, optimization and improvement of existing application using C#.

Also have experience and code debugging while following standard design patterns.

I have experience in analyzing business challenge and providing best solution in form of design and documentation.

I also analyze the business challenges and come up with the best algorithms following standard industry practice.

In my over 4-year experience I have grown to become full stack developer with frontend and backend development experience I have utilized HTML, CSS and JavaScript for Web application. I work on development of web and Mobile application as required.

Most applications I developed interact with different type of database on the backend which could either SQL or NoSQL database such as MongoDB, Postgres, MySQL amongst others.

I have very knowledgeable with technology stacks such as MVC, React for UI, Visual Studio .Net, C#, ASP.NET3.0, and ORM framework

(ORM: Object–relational mapping is a programming technique for converting data between incompatible type systems using object-oriented programming languages)

In my experience, I place priority on teamwork, collaboration and ensure every member of the team is fully engaged so that every aspect of the project progresses seamlessly

On most project I adopt the agile approach of software development in which we do daily stand up and have sprint in an iterative manner. I look forward to leveraging my skill, experience, and exposure in a challenging environment where I can make significant contribution to the success the organization application development.

Experience

Epoch Loop Technologies
.Net | C# backend developer
January 2021 - Present (3 years 1 month)
Lagos State, Nigeria

GIIT Africa Software Developer January 2020 - December 2020 (1 year) Lagos State, Nigeria

Education

The polytechnic, ibadan Electrical engineering (2016 - 2022)